CLENDA JEPKIRUI

CONTACT



🙎 Utawala, Nairobi, Kenya



((<u>1</u>)) 0795414896



glendabittok24@gmail.com

SKILLS

- · Self-possessed
- Creative
- Team player
- Equipment calibration
- Medical equipment maintenance
- Safety guidelines and procedures
- Programming
- Website building
- Hardware-software correlation
- First aid and Emergency approach

LANGUAGES

English, Swahili: First Language

REFERENCES

Kenya Medical Training Collage (KMTC)

Robinson Kisiangani - H.O.D, KMTC Loitokitok

rwanambacha@kmtc.ac.ke

Cell: +254720094037

Eldoret Hospital

Lameck Nawena

Lameckngwena1@gmail.com

Cell: +254740554203.

Reale Hospital Eldoret

Erick Simatwo - HOD

Cell; 0724059893, 0731680054

I'm a Biomedical Engineer and also a Software engineer from Moringa School bootcamp program which has made it possible to gain a thorough understanding of Software Engineering principals. Due to my passion for programming, I have a strong foundation in software development, with experience in programming languages such, Html, Css, JavaScript, Python, SQL and frameworks like React.js, Flask.py. I have successfully worked on various projects, including Asset inventory management system (Properties), which has enhanced my problem-solving skills and understanding of software design principles.

• Git account link, (Https://github.com/clenda24)which provides further details on my background and experience

EXPERIENCE

January 2023 - May 2023

Internship Biomedical Technologist Guru Nanak Ramgarhia Sikh, Nairobi, Kenya

- Performing all maintenance-related activities for all clinical and biomedical equipment, ancillaries, and accessories, i.e. Preventive, corrective, and calibration.
- Ensuring that all relevant records are accurately kept, maintained, and monitored, and any discrepancies are reported to the Biomedical Engineer.
- Participate in weekly cleaning (disinfection and rinsing), servicing, and general cleaning of the reverse osmosis renal water plant.
- Assist with service contracts on medical equipment, and ensure repair/installation work by contractors is carried out to the required standards.
- Attending training sessions on servicing new medical equipment.
- Assembling of new medical equipment.
- Any other duties assigned to do.

October 2021 - December 2021

Attachie Biomedical Technologist Eldoret Hospital, Eldolet , Kenya

- Repairing various medical equipment records.
- Providing technical support for medical equipment to the users.

Nakuru Provision General Hospital Simon Toroitich - HOD

Cell; 0727302758

- Assisting in data entry in the engineering spice work system.
- Undertaking electrical installations.
- Participate in weekly cleaning (disinfecting and rinsing), servicing, and general cleaning of the RO renal water plant.
- Attending training sessions on servicing new medical equipment.
- Assembling of new medical equipment, e.g. baby incubator, baby warmer, patient beds, patient monitors.
- Any other duties assigned to do.

April 2021 - June 2021

Attachie Biomedical Technologist Kapsabet County Referral Hospital, Kapsabet, Kenya

- Testing and carrying out electrical safety of new medical equipment.
- Attending training sessions on servicing new medical equipment.
- Repair and maintenance of medical equipment.
- Documenting and organising of medical equipment.
- Installation and assembling of new medical equipment, e.g. theatre lights.
- Any other duties assigned to do.

February 2019 - April 2019

Attachie Reale Hospital Eldoret, Eldoret, Kenya

- Testing and carrying out electrical safety of new medical equipment.
- Attending training sessions on servicing new medical equipment.
- Repair and maintenance of medical equipment, HVAC equipments and electrical Circuits/units
- Documenting and organising of medical equipment.
- Installation and assembling of new medical equipment.
- Any other duties assigned to do.

June 2018 - September 2018

Attachie Biomedical Technologist Nakuru Provincial General Hospital , Nakuru, Kenya

- Testing and carrying out caribrations of new medical equipment.
- Attending training sessions on servicing new medical equipment.
- Repair and maintenance of medical equipment.
- Documenting and organising of medical equipment.
- Assembling of new medical equipment.
- Any other duties assigned to do.

EDUCATION

2024

Boot-camp Program Software Engineering Moringa School, Nairobi

2022

Pass Biomedical/Medical Engineering
Kenya Medical Training Collage (KMTC), Loitokitok

• Diploma in Biomedical/Medical Engineering

2019

Pass Biomedical/Medical Engineering
Kenya Medical Training Collage (KMTC), Loitokitok

Certificate of Biomedical/Medical Engineering

2016

C Secondary education Segero Heralds Adventist High School , Uasin Gishu County

Kenya Secondary School Education

2012

310 Primary education Emdin Primary School, Nandi County

• Kenya Primary Education

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Software Design
- IOT Development
- Reading Journals
- Hackathons
- puzzle solving